Stephen Spielberg presents back to the future of Robert Zemeckis
film Marty leads an ordinary life. No McFly ever
amounted to anything in the history of Hill Valley. History is
going to change. And 1985 is not his
year. But Doctor Brown is about to change all that.
Are you telling me you built a time machine out of a DeLorean?
He's sending Marty 30 years back
in time. It works. It's a slurry
saucer from outer space. Now he's
trapped in the past. It's gotta be a dream. About to meet
chocolate, his future father. He's a beeping Tom.
Wow. And he's making an impression on
his mother. And he can sleep in my
room. Anything you do could have serious repercussions on
future events. Now he's got to make his mother and father
fall in love. For crying out loud. I haven't even been born yet.
And only Doctor Brown can help him
get back to the future.
Are you telling me that this sucker is nuclear?
Precisely. Michael J. Fox. Whoa, Sammy.
Christopher Lloyd. There's that word again. Heavy. Why are things
so heavy in the future? Is there a problem with the earth's gravitational pull to
the future?