Fairy tales can come true?
It can happen to you if you're
young at heart. Mirror, mirror on the wall is this not
the most perfect kingdom of them all? Well, technically,
it's not perfect. Uh,
Thelonious,
you were saying? Twas long ago and far away?
In a land as different as night from day?
Fairy tale creatures are a magical sort? I'm not a puppet.
I'm a real boy.
This one's full. Take it away. We're banished by a prince
who was really short? He hoofed and he puffed and he
signed an eviction notice? You're a monster now,
the one to save their neck. Oh, you're expecting Prince
Charming? Hey. Oh, no, no,
no. Gent girl, off the table. Where are we supposed to put her?
The bed's taken. What is a
hero named Shrek? Shrek. Shrek.
Shrek.
That was really scary. And if you don't mind me saying, you definitely need
some tic tacs or something. Cause your breath stinks. But a tail like this will
also need a princess.
What? And a noble steed. All right,
I hope you heard that. You called me a noble steed? You think I'm a
steed? Mike Myers? Eddie Murphy? Cameron Diaz.
John Lithgow? This is gonna be fun. We can stay up late swapping manly
stories in the morning. I'm making waffles. Then I saw
her face. Don't look down.
You think that Shrek. If you do, love. Well, yes,
Shrek. I just know before this is over, I'm gonna need a whole lot of
serious therapy. Look at my eye twitching.