Where do we begin? A year ago
these cops and lawyers wouldn't dare cross
any of you. I mean, what happened?
So, what are you proposing? Simple. Kill the
Batman.
Here's my card.
Bruce, this is Harvey Dent. Rachel's told me everything about you.
I certainly hope not.
You once told me that we'd be together. Did you mean it?
Bruce? Don't make me your only hope for a normal life.
You're Alfred, right? That's right, sir. Any psychotic ex boyfriends
I should be aware? Oh, you have no idea.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
We're tonight's entertainment. Well,
hello, beautiful.
You look nervous. I've seen
now what have to become to stop men like him.
The night is darkest just before the dawn. I promise
you the dawn is coming.
And here we go.
Come on.
This city deserves a better class of criminal.
I'm gonna give it to him. No.
You'll see. I'll show you.
You either die a hero or you live long
enough to see yourself become the villain.
Will you be wanting the bat pod, sir? Middle of the day, Alfred. Not very
subtle. The Lamborghini, then.
Much more subtle.